home_page_stepper: SELEZIONA IL TUO MERCATO
select_your_market:Seleziona il Tuo Mercato
select_your_language:Seleziona il Tuo Linguaggio
franchise_partner:DISTRIBUTORE
preferred_customer:PREFERRED CUSTOMER
join_as_fp_desc:Avviando un business Unicity, Sarai in grado di guadagnare profitti significativi e stabili, così come fare bonus generosi.
join_as_pc_desc:By joining Unicity as a Preferred Customer, you'll receive an instant discount on all Unicity products.
footer_need_help: Ti serve aiuto?

footer_executive_support_it:Il supporto al cliente +41-41-5 111 333
footer_hours_it:M-F, 08:00 – 17:00 CET
footer_email:service.management@unicity.com
footer_branding_it:Copyright Unicity Italy Srl

footer_hours_ch:M-F, 08:00 – 17:00 CET
intiailorder:INITIAL ORDER
start_with_product:Start with a Product or Business pack
choose_your_pack:Choose your pack type
pick_your_pack:Pick Your Pack
add_additional_products:Add additional products
search_product:Search Products by...Name or Item code
clear:Clear
all_a-z:All products A-Z
suggested_products:Suggested products
added_additional_products:Additional products added
summary:Summary
initial_order:Initial Order
qty:QTY
item:Item #
pv:PV
price:PRICE
subtotal:Subtotal

monthly_auto-refill:MONTHLY AUTO-REFILL
setup_ar:Would you like to set up a monthly Auto Refill?
ar_yes:Yes
ar_no:No, thank you
set_up_ar:Set Up Monthly Auto Refill
skip_ar:Skip this step >
more_popular_products:Would you like to add more popular products?
monthly_ar:Monthly Auto-Refill

Maschile : male
Femminile : female


it :[Impostazioni di Iscrizione, Informazioni su di te, Opzioni per il Pagamento della Commissione, Il tuo Ufficio Unicity, ]
eu_ch :[Impostazioni di Iscrizione, Informazioni su di te, Coniuge richiedente/Compagnia (opzionale), Opzioni per il Pagamento della Commissione, Il tuo Ufficio Unicity]
payment_eu :[Payment Options, Informazioni Della Carta di Credito, Indirizzo di Fatturazione, Indirizzo di spedizione, Metodo di spedizione]
payment_ch :[Payment Options, Informazioni Della Carta di Credito, Indirizzo di Fatturazione, Indirizzo di spedizione, Metodo di spedizione]
summary_it :[Sommario Dell'Iscrizione, Impostazioni di Iscrizione, A proposito di te, Opzioni per il Pagamento della Commissione, Il tuo indirizzo di consegna, Il tuo indirizzo di fatturazione/indirizzo primario, Le tue informazioni di pagamento, Termini e Condizioni, Sommario]
summary_ch :[Sommario Dell'Iscrizione, Enrollment Settings, Informazioni su di te, Coniuge richiedente/Compagnia, Opzioni per il Pagamento della Commissione, Il tuo indirizzo di consegna, Il tuo indirizzo di fatturazione/indirizzo primario, Le tue informazioni di pagamento, Termini e Condizioni, Sommario]

IT : Italy
CH : Switzerland


bankwire_it :Thank you for your payment by bank transfer! Please note the following points so that your order can be processed quickly:\nPlease transfer the full amount to:\nAccount Name: Unicity Italy Sarl\nIBAN: IT81P0349401600000060100034\nBIC: CHASITMX\nPlease enter your ID or order number in the reason for payment field.\nWe will ship your order as soon as we have received the amount due.\nThe PV of the order will also be credited upon receipt of payment.\nLate payment may affect your qualification for the compensation plan – so better transfer the money quickly.\nThank you very much! We hope you enjoy the Unicity products.
bankwire_ch :Thank you for your payment by bank transfer! Please note the following points so that your order can be processed quickly:\nPlease transfer the full amount to:\nAccount Name: Unicity Global Markets GmbH\nIBAN: CH210027327326928801E\nBIC: UBSWCHZH80A\nPlease enter your ID or order number in the reason for payment field.\nWe will ship your order as soon as we have received the amount due.\nThe PV of the order will also be credited upon receipt of payment.\nLate payment may affect your qualification for the compensation plan – so better transfer the money quickly.\nThank you very much! We hope you enjoy the Unicity products.